<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome on anmorris.org</title>
    <link>http://anmorris.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome on anmorris.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 20:19:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://anmorris.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A brief review of Black Ops 4</title>
      <link>http://anmorris.org/blog/a_brief_review_of_bo4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 20:19:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://anmorris.org/blog/a_brief_review_of_bo4/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t intend to use this blog solely for game reviews, but since I have a few people interested in my thoughts on the new Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 I will put my thoughts here because it honestly will be easier to write here than on my phone or in chat. As an aside, I have two other new posts in progress but one involves a project I&amp;rsquo;m not ready to reveal yet, and another is regarding some personal research I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing on Programming Language Expressiveness &amp;amp; Safety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Beginnings</title>
      <link>http://anmorris.org/blog/new_beginnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 13:58:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://anmorris.org/blog/new_beginnings/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my new personal website. This is mostly a site so I can post my personal projects, blog a little about them and other things, and have a presence that I have control over (unlike Facebook/Twitter/etc.) on the internet.
I&amp;rsquo;ll be posting more in a couple days, including the progress on this site. I still need to finish:
 RSS Export Add current Projects Add past Projects Add more Social Networking information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About this Site</title>
      <link>http://anmorris.org/about/site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2018 22:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://anmorris.org/about/site/</guid>
      <description>Every project we work on tends to be a learning experience. Sometimes we learn new technologies, sometimes we learn things about ourselves, and sometimes we learn life lessons. This project that led to the creation of this website fit into the life lessons category.
It&amp;rsquo;s taken 3 years, working on and off, for this simple website to take shape. If that sounds insane, you&amp;rsquo;re absolutely right, it is. In actuality, this is probably the 4th or 5th iteration of the site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://anmorris.org/about/me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://anmorris.org/about/me/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re here, you probably are interested who I am and what I do. I&amp;rsquo;m Adam Morris, a Software Engineer located in the Midwestern United States. If you dig around you can probably figure out who I work for, but I generally don&amp;rsquo;t care to share that info. I grew up in Georgia, attended Georgia College &amp;amp; State University in Milledgeville for my Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Computer Science, and I attended Iowa State University several years later for a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Human-Computer Interaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Me</title>
      <link>http://anmorris.org/social/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://anmorris.org/social/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Useful Tools &amp; Other Links</title>
      <link>http://anmorris.org/social/useful-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://anmorris.org/social/useful-links/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>